A Guide to the Asian Cultural Council records, Grants, RG 5 FA1403
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Art History, 1964-2005; 6; 16.13 Cubic Feet 39 letter document boxes and 1 record storage box
  - Thailand, 6.18
    - Woodward, Hiram W., Jr., Yale University, B-7156, DF-71116, B-72107, 1971-1972 (Box 488, Folder 8)
    - Krasiriksh, Piriya (Hoy), Harvard University, B-7105, EC-7131, B-7531, DF-7577, B-7429, DF-7580, 1971-1975 (Box 489, Folder 1)
    - Brown, Robert L., EC-7664, 1976 (Box 489, Folder 2)
    - Mani, Weerwan, B-7735, B-7832, 1977-1978 (Box 489, Folder 3)
    - McGill, Forrest, B-7629, B-7676, 1976 (Box 489, Folder 4)
    - Harvard University, DF-8901 (cancelled), 1989 (Box 489, Folder 5)
    - Matics, Kathleen, B-7646, DF-7790, 1976-1977 (Box 490, Folder 1)
    - Brown, Roxanna, 706-00-20087-203.1, 2000 (Box 490, Folder 2)
    - Stratton, Carol, 707-00-98051-203.1, 1998 (Box 490, Folder 3)
  - Vietnam, 6.19
    - Nguyen, Trian, 706-00-94063-203.000-1, 1994 (Box 490, Folder 4)
    - Bang, Thuc-Ban, 703-00-98102-203.1, 703-00-97147-203.1, 536-00-97135-203.4, 703-00-96097-203.1, 703-00-7023-203.2 (Box 490, Folder 5)
    - Cort, Louis and Lefferts, Horace Leedom, Jr., 706-00-22089-203.1, 2002 (Box 490, Folder 6)
    - Phuong, Tran Ky, 100-00-24139-203.3, 2004 (Box 490, Folder 7)
- Arts Administration, 2002-2005; 7; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
  - China, 7.1
    - Yu, Ding, 696-00-23058-203.1, 2003 (Box 491, Folder 1)
    - Li, Ming, 100-00-22141-203.3, 100-00-22011-203.2, 2002 (Box 491, Folder 2)
  - India, 7.2
    - Battery Dance Company, 100-00-22058-203.1, 2002 (Box 491, Folder 3)
  - Indonesia, 7.3
    - Wastika, Alia, 615-00-25139-203.4, 2005 (Box 492, Folder 1)
  - Korea, 7.4
    - Sohn, Hee-Jeong, 100-00-23009-203.2, 100-00-22055-203.1, 100-00-20047-203.1 (Box 492, Folder 2)
  - Philippines, 7.5
    - Bernardo, Carmencita, 655-00-23026-203.2, 2003 (Box 492, Folder 3)
  - Vietnam, 7.6
    - Dung, Nguyen Kim, 634-00-25016-203.2, 2005 (Box 492, Folder 4)
- Cinematography-Photography, 1964-2003; 8; 13.29 Cubic Feet 35 letter document boxes
  - Asia, 8.1
    - Cine-Asia, Barnouw, Erick, B-7280, 1972 (Box 493, Folder 1)
    - Asia Society, DF-8992, 1989 (Box 493, Folder 2)
    - Asian Cinema Studies Society, 3rd International Film Conference, D. Desser, B-9188(56), 1991 (Box 493, Folder 3)
    - Farber, Donald, B-9336(77), 1993 (Box 493, Folder 4)
    - Asian Cinevision, EC-9204, DF-88126, 1988; 1992 (Box 493, Folder 5)
    - Schreibman, Jane, B-9337(77), 1993 (Box 493, Folder 6)
    - Hawaii International Film Festival, B-9370(56), 1993 (Box 493, Folder 7)
    - Steiner, Charles, B-86110, 1986 (Box 493, Folder 8)
    - Asia Pacific Media Center, 100-00-98010-203.2, 1998 (Box 493, Folder 9)
    - International Film Seminars, 100-00-21021-203.2, 2001 (Box 493, Folder 10)
    - Independent Television Service, 100-00-23133-203.3, 2003 (Box 494, Folder 1)
    - International Film Seminars, Inc., 100-00-23042-203.1, 2003 (Box 494, Folder 2)
  - Bangladesh, 8.2
    - Global Village Resource Center, B-7350, 1973 (Box 494, Folder 3)
  - Cambodia, 8.3
    - Washington, D. C. International Film Festival, DF-8919, 1989 (Box 494, Folder 4)
  - China, 8.4
    - Stanford University, DF-7561, 1975 (Box 494, Folder 5)
    - Cinematography-China, Davenport, Thomas, B-6952, 1969 (Box 494, Folder 6)
    - Cinema and Photography-China, Jin, Bohong, R-8212(16), 1982 (Box 494, Folder 7)
    - Cinematography-China, Center for US-China Arts Exchange, DF-8795, 1987 (Box 494, Folder 8)
    - Bai, Ling,, DF-8982, 1989 (Box 494, Folder 9)
    - Mu, Shulan, EC-8984, Cancelled, 1989 (Box 494, Folder 10)
    - Fotofest, 100-00-96006-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 495, Folder 1)
    - Reynaud, Berenice, 706-00-97079-203.1, 1997 (Box 495, Folder 2)
    - Peng, Xiao Lian, EC-9012, 1990 (Box 495, Folder 3)
    - Dong, Xinyu, 100-00-99036-203.1, 1999 (Box 495, Folder 4)
    - Choy, Christine, 517-00-97149-203.1, 1997 (Box 495, Folder 5)
    - Liu, Dong, 100-00-99010-203.2, 1999 (Box 495, Folder 6)
    - Liu, Xiao Jin, 703-00-20115-203.1, 2000 (Box 496, Folder 1)
    - Meyer, Richard, 706-00-20087-203.1, 2000 (Box 496, Folder 2)
    - New York University, 100-00-21005-203.3, 2001 (Box 496, Folder 3)
    - Wu, Tianming, B-8836, 1988 (Box 496, Folder 4)
    - Chan, Mark Kam Lok, 529-00-97070-203.000-1, 1997 (Box 496, Folder 5)
    - Appalshop, 100-00-24046-203.1, 2004 (Box 497, Folder 1)
    - Appalshop, 100-00-22057-203.1, 2002 (Box 497, Folder 2)
    - Liu, Xiaojin, 100-00-23128-203.3, 2003 (Box 497, Folder 3)
    - Wu, Wenguang, 100-00-96033-203.000.1, 100-00-20153.3 (Box 497, Folder 4)
    - Zhang, Yuan, 703-00-95093-203.000-1, 703-00-97022-203.000-2, 1995; 1997 (Box 498, Folder 1)
    - Xing, Danwen, 703-00-20020-203.2, 703-00-99100.1, 1999; 2000 (Box 498, Folder 2)
    - Yang, Yun, 703-00-25113-203.1, 2005 (Box 499, Folder 1)
  - Hong Kong, 8.5
    - Lo, Grace, B-8931, B-8860(HK)R, 1988; 1989 (Box 499, Folder 2)
    - Mo, Comyn (Man Yu), B-9047(HK), 1990 (Box 499, Folder 3)
    - Wan, Man-kit, B-9049(HK), 1990 (Box 499, Folder 4)
    - Chu, Tak Wah (Almond), DD-93101(405), 1993 (Box 499, Folder 5)
    - Fung, John, B-8858(HK)R, 1988 (Box 500, Folder 1)
    - Fung, May Mei-wah, B-9354(HK), 1993 (Box 500, Folder 2)
    - Pau, Ellen, B-9165(27), 1991 (Box 500, Folder 3)
    - Boyle, Deirdre, 706-00-97078-203.000-1, 1997 (Box 500, Folder 4)
    - Kwan, Pun Leung, 474-00-97104-203.000-4, 1997 (Box 500, Folder 5)
    - London, Barbara, 450-00-95112-203.000-2, 1995 (Box 500, Folder 6)
    - So, Hing Keung, 452-00-95055-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 501, Folder 1)
    - Wong, Mary, 452-00-95056-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 501, Folder 2)
    - Cheung, Chi Wai, 502-00-96061-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 501, Folder 3)
    - The Kitchen, 100-00-98025-203.3, 1998 (Box 501, Folder 4)
    - Hung, Wing Kit, 652-00-22080-203.1 (Box 501, Folder 5)
    - Wong, Holly Lee, 451-00-94052-203.000-1, 1994 (Box 501, Folder 6)
    - Yeung, Hei, 507-00-97069-203.000-1, 1997 (Box 502, Folder 1)
    - Leung, Warren, 100-00-99151-203.3, 529-00-97071-203.1, 1997; 1999 (Box 502, Folder 2)
    - Mak, Anson, 690-00-23060-203.1, 2003 (Box 502, Folder 3)
  - India, 8.6
    - Cine-Photo-India, Elbers, Johan E., B-7354, B-7451, 1973-1974 (Box 503, Folder 1)
    - Cine-India, Patel, Ishu (Ishwarbhai), B-7103, 1971 (Box 503, Folder 2)
    - Cinematography-India, Van Dyke, Willard, MoMA, DF-6709, DF-6919, 1967; 1969 (Box 503, Folder 3)
    - Cinematography-India, Welch, Cary, Fogg Art Museum, and Clark Worswick, B-6780, B-6987, 1967; 1969 (Box 503, Folder 4)
    - Cine-India, Dayasaran, DF-6681, 1966 (Box 503, Folder 5)
    - Cinematography-India, Asia Society, Peters, Muriel, B-7854, 1978 (Box 503, Folder 6)
    - Cinematography-India, Mathur, I. S., IIE, B-6675, EC-6905, 1966; 1969 (Box 503, Folder 7)
    - Film-India, Candoth, Krishna, B-8514, 1985 (Box 503, Folder 8)
    - Asia Society, Film India, B-8102, 1981 (Box 504, Folder 1)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, DF-8502, 1985 (Box 504, Folder 2)
    - Singh, Ragubir, B-9076(27), 1990 (Box 504, Folder 3)
    - Salvo, Dean, B-9248(77), 1992 (Box 504, Folder 4)
    - Bartholomew, Pablo, B-8778(27)R, 1987 (Box 504, Folder 5)
    - Benegal, Dev, EC-8910, B-89105, 1989 (Box 504, Folder 6)
    - Richie, Donal, MoMA, DF-6843, B-6986, 1968; 1969 (Box 505, Folder 1)
    - Bhagat, Darshan, 100-00-94112-203.000-3, B-9388(27), 1993; 1994 (Box 505, Folder 2)
    - Mukherjee, Suman, 100-00-96110-203.3, 100-00-97143-203.3, 1996; 1997 (Box 505, Folder 3)
    - Houseal, Joseph, 706-00-21030-203.2, 2001 (Box 505, Folder 4)
    - Kahn, Nathaniel, 706-00-98073-203.1, 1998 (Box 505, Folder 5)
    - Mukherjee, Suman, 100-00-21017-203.2, 2001 (Box 505, Folder 6)
  - Indonesia, 8.7
    - Reed, C. Lawson, III, B-7855, 1978 (Box 506, Folder 1)
    - Hakim, Christine, DF-8306, 1983 (Box 506, Folder 2)
    - Datau, Surayuddin, 100-00-22010-203.3, 2002 (Box 506, Folder 3)
    - Cinema and Photography-Indoensia, Amriradhiani, 615-00-25137-203.4, 2005 (Box 506, Folder 4)
    - Setiawati, Sri Ranta, 615-00-23116-203.4, 2003 (Box 506, Folder 5)
    - Wibowo, Daryanto, 702-00-26059-203.1, 615-00-24125-203.4 (Box 507, Folder 1)
  - Japan, 8.8
    - Vanderbeek, Stan, Cine-Japan, B-6985, 1969 (Box 507, Folder 2)
    - Vanderbeek, Stan, B-6985, 1969 (Box 507, Folder 3)
    - University of Washington (Nomura Film), B-6403, 1964 (Box 507, Folder 4)
    - Ross, David, Project Related Materials, B-7520, 1975 (Box 507, Folder 5)
    - Szarkowski, John, MoMA, B-7155, 1971 (Box 508, Folder 1)
    - Staples, Donald E., DF-7535, 1975 (Box 508, Folder 2)
    - Ross, David, Long Beach Museum of Art, California, B-7520, 1975 (Box 508, Folder 3)
    - Matsumoto, Toshio, Open Circuits, DF-7477, 1974 (Box 508, Folder 4)
    - Abe, Shuya, California Institute of Arts, B-7214, 1972 (Box 508, Folder 5)
    - Hani, Susumo, DF-7586, 1975 (Box 508, Folder 6)
    - Japan Society (Films of Japanese Artists), 6412, 1964 (Box 508, Folder 7)
    - Japan, Ishizaki, Koichiro, DF-6848, 1968 (Box 508, Folder 8)
    - Ichioka, Yasuko, International Film and TV Seminar, DF-72118, 1972 (Box 508, Folder 9)
    - Japan, Japan Society, The Arts of Shinto, DF-7737, 1977 (Box 508, Folder 10)
    - Shigeo Anzai, "Recording", Photographs, At the Kitchen, 1970 June 7-17 (Box 944, Folder 2)
    - Anzai, Shigeo, B-7915, 1979 (Box 508, Folder 11)
    - American Film Institute, B-8519, 1985 (Box 509, Folder 1)
    - Hoberman, James, DF8544, 1985 (Box 509, Folder 2)
    - Innocent Eyes and Lenses, DF-8470, DF-8681, 1984; 1986 (Box 509, Folder 3)
    - The Japan Society, DF-8667, 1986 (Box 509, Folder 4)
    - Kawanaka, Nobuhiro (JUSAP), B-8462(30)R, 1984 (Box 509, Folder 5)
    - Nakajima, Ko, DF-8204, 1982 (Box 509, Folder 6)
    - Bunnell, Peter C., B-8427(30)R, 1984 (Box 509, Folder 7)
    - Calmes, Alan, B-9150(30), 1991 (Box 509, Folder 8)
    - Desser, David, EC-9209(56), 1992 (Box 509, Folder 9)
    - Erlich, Linda, EC-9009(30), 1990 (Box 509, Folder 10)
    - Haar, Tom, DF-8547, 1985 (Box 510, Folder 1)
    - Kobayashi, Kazuo, B-9063(30), 1990 (Box 510, Folder 2)
    - Mickalik, Chester, B-9070(30), 1990 (Box 510, Folder 3)
    - Oakland University, B-89116(30), 1989 (Box 510, Folder 4)
    - Yamagami, Sumiko, B-86106(30)R, 1986 (Box 510, Folder 5)
    - Gorewitz, Shalom, B-9151(30), 1991 (Box 510, Folder 6)
    - Idemitsu, Mako, B-8595(30)R, 1985 (Box 510, Folder 7)
    - KQED, B-8640(30)R, 1986 (Box 510, Folder 8)
    - McDonald, Keiko, EC-9310(30), 1993 (Box 511, Folder 1)
    - Museum of Modern Art, DF-9313, 1993 (Box 511, Folder 2)
    - Noletti, Arthur, Jr., EC-9210(56), 1992 (Box 511, Folder 3)
    - Sasaki, Tomiyo, B-9157(30), 1991 (Box 511, Folder 4)
    - Pacific Basin Institute, EC-9112(30), 1991 (Box 511, Folder 5)
    - Turner, Judith, B-8583(30)R, 1985 (Box 511, Folder 6)
    - Wada, Warner, B-9152(30), 1991 (Box 511, Folder 7)
    - Anzai, Shigeo, B-7915, 1979 (Box 511, Folder 8)
    - De Melo, Jacques, B-9384, 1993 (Box 512, Folder 1)
    - Bubriski, Kevin, 704-00-94075-203.000-1, 1994 (Box 512, Folder 2)
    - Hara Museum of Contemporary Art, 704-95084-1, 95085-1, 1995 (Box 512, Folder 3)
    - Rubinfien, Leo, B-8429(30)R, 1984 (Box 512, Folder 4)
    - Takahashi, Kyoko, B-8760(30)R, 1987 (Box 512, Folder 5)
    - Brown, Sheldon, 704-00-96082-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 512, Folder 6)
    - Films for Humanity, 704-00-96087-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 513, Folder 1)
    - Funches, Tracy, 704-00-20099-203.1, 2000 (Box 513, Folder 2)
    - Klochko, Deborah, 704-00-97094-203.000-1, 1997 (Box 513, Folder 3)
    - Kurita, Koichiro, B-9064(30), 1990 (Box 513, Folder 4)
    - Lopez, August, 704-00-99086-203.00.1, 1999 (Box 513, Folder 5)
    - Pacific Film Archive, University of California Berkeley, 704-00-22106-203.1, 2002 (Box 513, Folder 6)
    - Noguchi, Rika, 500-00-97089-203.000-1, 1997 (Box 514, Folder 1)
    - Diggs, Isaac, 704-00-24083-203.1, 2004 (Box 514, Folder 2)
    - Ding, Loni, B-8578(30)R, 1985 (Box 514, Folder 3)
    - Miyamoto, Ryuji, B-9077(27), 1990 (Box 514, Folder 4)
    - Richie, Donald, JDR 3rd Award, B-93119(39), 1993 (Box 514, Folder 5)
    - Rubenfien, 706-00-22088-203.1, 2002 (Box 515, Folder 1)
    - Ross, David, Project Related Materials, B-7520, 1975 (Box 941, Folder 2)
  - Korea, 8.9
    - Cine-Korea, Museum of Modern Art, DF-7589, 1975 (Box 515, Folder 2)
    - Lim, Young Kyun (Box 944, Folder 1)
    - Kim, Young-im, B-8592(27)R, 1985 (Box 515, Folder 3)
    - Seoul Institute of the Arts, DF-8302, 1983 (Box 515, Folder 4)
    - Fitzgerald, Kit, DF-9090, 1990 (Box 515, Folder 5)
    - Fotofest, 703-00-20022-203.2, 2000 (Box 516, Folder 1)
    - Ha, Joon Soo, 703-00-230105-203.1, 703-00-22123-203.1, 703-00-21129-203.1 (Box 516, Folder 2)
    - Kim, Jeong Han, 703-00-25118-203.1, 2005 (Box 516, Folder 3)
    - Lee, Hyun Jean, 703-00-23106-203.1, 703-00-22124-203.1, 2003 (Box 517, Folder 1)
  - Nepal, 8.10
    - Cinematography -Nepal, Asia Society, Nepal: Where the Gods Are Young, DF-7753, 1977 (Box 517, Folder 2)
  - Philippines, 8.11
    - Aguiluz, Amable R.,(TICOY), Cine-Philippines, EC-7759, 1977 (Box 517, Folder 3)
    - Cinema and Photography-Philippines, Aguiluz, Amable R., EC-7759, DF-7788, 1977 (Box 517, Folder 4)
    - Cinematography-Philippines, Francia, Henry, DF-6861, DF-6862, B-6943, 1968-1969 (Box 517, Folder 5)
    - Cinematography -Philippines, Francia, Henry, Cinematheque Manila Foundation, B-7258-AIP, 1972 (Box 518, Folder 1)
    - Wesleyan University, DF-89120, 1989 (Box 518, Folder 2)
    - International Film Seminars, Inc., 100-00-94095-203.000-3, 1994 (Box 518, Folder 3)
    - Asian Cinevision, 100-00-22134-203.1, 2002 (Box 518, Folder 4)
    - Aguiluz, Amable Tikoy, 100-00-99026-203.3, 1999 (Box 518, Folder 5)
    - Cinemanila International Film Festival, 100-00-20004-203.3 (Box 518, Folder 6)
    - Cinemanila International Film Festival, 100-00-20138-203.3, 2000 (Box 519, Folder 1)
    - Corre, Fruto, B-92-87(327), 1992 (Box 519, Folder 2)
    - Palasi, Kathleen, B-93120(27), 1993 (Box 519, Folder 3)
    - Walker Arts Center, 100-00-97007-203.000-2, 1997 (Box 519, Folder 4)
    - Carolino, Edita, 655-00-23094-203.1, 2003 (Box 519, Folder 5)
    - Cinemanila International Film Festival, 655-00-23098, 2003 (Box 519, Folder 6)
    - Dalena, Sari, 703-00-24107-203.1, 655-00-23100-203.1, 703-00-22125-203.1, 2003; 2004 (Box 520, Folder 1)
    - Palasi, Kathleen, 703-00-24108-203.1, 2004 (Box 520, Folder 2)
    - Panaligan, Raymond, 703-00-99102-203.000-1, 1999 (Box 520, Folder 3)
    - Shaw, Angel Velasco, 100-00-98124-203.3, 494-0097051-203.1, 517-00-97052-203.1, 1997-1998 (Box 520, Folder 4)
  - Sri Lanka, 8.12
    - Cinema-Sri Lanka, Hannemann, Yvonne, Bank St. College of Education, B-7161, DF-7188, B-7262, 1971-1972 (Box 521, Folder 1)
    - Hanneman, Yvonne, DF-7188, 1971 (Box 943, Folder 2)
    - Asian Cinevision, DF-9084, 1990 (Box 521, Folder 2)
  - Taiwan, 8.13
    - Lu, Tonglin, B-9269(56), 1992 (Box 521, Folder 3)
    - Wang, Jun-Jieh, 703-00-95095-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 521, Folder 4)
  - Thailand, 8.14
    - Kosalwat, Banchong, Cine-Thailand (Box 521, Folder 5)
    - Cinematography -Thailand, Kosalwat, Banchong, B-7530, B-7627, B-7831, 1975-1978 (Box 522, Folder 1)
    - Cinema-Thailand, Krebs, Stephanie Laird, DF-7187, B-7271, B-7301, DF-7383, DF-7936, 1971-1979 (Box 522, Folder 2)
    - Jarernporn, Penpan, DF-8507, 1985 (Box 522, Folder 3)
    - Thongsang, Pantham, B-9289(327), 1992 (Box 522, Folder 4)
    - Yerba Buena Center for the Arts, 703-00-24116-203.1, 2004 (Box 522, Folder 5)
  - Tibet, 8.15
    - New York Women in Film, DF-9292, 1992 (Box 522, Folder 6)
    - Tibet Film Festival, DF-9173, 1991 (Box 523, Folder 1)
  - Vietnam, 8.16
    - Asian Cinevision, 100-00-94001-203.000-3, 1994 (Box 523, Folder 2)
    - McMahon, Kathryn, Hanoi National Pedagogic University, 479-00-96046-203.000-1, 494-00-96047-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 523, Folder 3)
    - Fotofest, 100-00-97155-203.3, 1997 (Box 523, Folder 4)
    - Robinson, Abby-Vietnamese Artistic Photography, 494-00-96048-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 523, Folder 5)
    - Samuelson, Kristine, 100-00-22157-203.3, 2002 (Box 523, Folder 6)
    - Connors, Richard, 494-00-96120-203.1, 1996 (Box 523, Folder 7)
    - Hanoi Institute of Theatre and Cinema, 100-00-20163-203.3, 100-00-20056-203.1, 2000 (Box 524, Folder 1)
- Crafts, 1966-2005; 9; 3.8 Cubic Feet 10 letter document boxes
  - Asia, 9.1
    - World Crafts Council, Crafts-Asia, B-6870, B-7046, 1970 (Box 524, Folder 2)
    - American Committee, World Crafts Council, B-6870, B-7046, EC-7480, 1968; 1974 (Box 524, Folder 3)
    - World Crafts Council, American Committee, Kyoto 1978, B-7901, 1978-1979 (Box 525, Folder 1)
    - World Print Council, DF-8245, 1982 (Box 525, Folder 2)
    - Aid to Artisans, Inc., DF-8501, 1985 (Box 525, Folder 3)
  - Afghanistan, 9.2
    - Johnston, Robert, B-7447, 1974 (Box 526, Folder 1)
    - Arzu, 706-00-24007-203.2, 2004 (Box 526, Folder 2)
  - China, 9.3
    - William D. Y. Wu, B-7449, DF-7651, 1974; 1976 (Box 526, Folder 3)
    - Ho, Chuimei, B-9243(314), 1992 (Box 526, Folder 4)
    - New York State College of Ceramics at Alfred University, 703-00-95099-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 526, Folder 5)
    - Woo, Marie, 706-00-97077-203.00-1, 1997 (Box 526, Folder 6)
    - Tu, Hengxian, B-9253(26), 1992 (Box 527, Folder 1)
    - New York State College of Ceramics at Alfred University, 703-00-20122-203.1, 2000 (Box 527, Folder 2)
    - Stephenson, John, 706-00-20017-203.2, 2000 (Box 527, Folder 3)
    - Smithsonian Institution, 702-00-22018-203.2 (Box 527, Folder 4)
  - India, 9.4
    - Crafts Museum, New Delhi, B-7538-AIP, 1975 (Box 527, Folder 5)
    - Untracht, Alvin J. (Oppi), B-7356, 1973 (Box 527, Folder 6)
    - Kak, Krishen Kumsar, DF-8556, 1985 (Box 527, Folder 7)
    - The Clay Studio, Jagdish Pandit, 703-00-23029-203.2, 2003 (Box 527, Folder 8)
    - Mehra, Priya Ravish, 702-00-25053-203.1, 2005 (Box 527, Folder 9)
  - Indonesia, 9.5
    - Crews, Patricia Cox, B-93117(314), 1993 (Box 528, Folder 1)
  - Japan, 9.6
    - Nakamura, Kimpei, B-7039, 1970 (Box 528, Folder 2)
    - Nakamura, Kimpei, B-6614, 1966 (Box 528, Folder 3)
    - Ellis, Charles Grant, B-8579(30)R, 1985 (Box 528, Folder 4)
    - Ikrhata, Hiroshi, B-8796(30)R, 1989 (Box 528, Folder 5)
    - Greenwich House Pottery, DF-8809, 1988 (Box 528, Folder 6)
    - Hurwitz, H. Michael, B-9069(30), 1990 (Box 528, Folder 7)
    - Kelso, James D., B-87101(30)R, 1987 (Box 529, Folder 1)
    - Okuda, Hiromu, B-8966(30), 1989 (Box 529, Folder 2)
    - Nakamoto, Tomoko, 704-00-94071-203.000-1, 1994 (Box 529, Folder 3)
    - SUNY College at New Paltz, 704-00-94085-203.000-1, 1994 (Box 529, Folder 4)
    - Archie Bray Foundation for the Ceramic Arts, 100-00-20152-203.3, 2000 (Box 529, Folder 5)
    - San Francisco Craft and Folk Museum, 100-00-96099-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 529, Folder 6)
    - Nicholas, Donna L., 704-00-95082-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 529, Folder 7)
    - Kosugi, Takuya and Nagata, Kazuhiro, 100-00-22034-203.3, 2002 (Box 529, Folder 8)
    - Stinchecum, Amanda, 704-00-99088-203.000-1, 1999 (Box 530, Folder 1)
    - Weiser, Kurt, 704-002-98086-203.1, 1998 (Box 530, Folder 2)
    - Morris, Joan, 704-00-25011-203.2, 2005 (Box 530, Folder 3)
    - Franck, Fance, EC-8712(30)R, 1987 (Box 633, Folder 6)
    - Franck, Fance, 1987-1991 (Box 634, Folder 1)
  - Korea, 9.7
    - duBois, Ronald, B-7499, 1974 (Box 530, Folder 4)
    - North Carolina Pottery Center, 100-00-21002-203.3, 2001 (Box 530, Folder 5)
  - Laos, 9.8
    - Museum of Craft and Folk Art, 702-00-23053-203.1, 2003 (Box 530, Folder 6)
  - Nepal, 9.9
    - Chase, Judith Conant, DF-7941, 1979 (Box 530, Folder 7)
  - Sri Lanka, 9.10
    - Sansoni, Barbara, B-7058, 1970 (Box 530, Folder 8)
  - Thailand, 9.11
    - Natewong, Suwanee, B-9079(27), 1990 (Box 530, Folder 9)
  - Vietnam, 9.12
    - Lefferts, Leedom H., Jr., B-8963(56), 1989 (Box 531, Folder 1)
    - Aid to Artisans, 100-00-95011-203.000-3, 1995 (Box 531, Folder 2)
- Dance, 1964-2006; 10; 23.17 Cubic Feet 61 letter document boxes
  - Asia, 10.1
    - Paul Taylor's Dance Company, Dance-Asia, Other than Correspondence, B-6759, 1967 (Box 531, Folder 3)
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music, Darpana Dance Co. and Dance of Bali, B-7347, 1973 (Box 531, Folder 4)
    - Martha Graham Dance Company, EC-74114, 1974 (Box 531, Folder 5)
    - Paul Taylor's Dance Co., B-6759, 1967 (Box 531, Folder 6)
    - Merce Cunningham Dance Company, ANTA, 6422, (6410 Canceled), 1964 (Box 531, Folder 7)
    - New York Public Library, Dance-Asia, B-7659, 1976 (Box 532, Folder 1)
    - American Dance Guild, CORD (Committee on Research in Dance), EC-7866, 1978 (Box 532, Folder 2)
    - New York Public Library-Dance Archives, B-7652, EV-7659, B-7742, 1976-1977 (Box 532, Folder 3)
    - New York Public Library, Dance Archives, B-7652, EC-7629, B-7742, 1976-1977 (Box 532, Folder 4)
    - American Dance Festival, DF-8506, B-8417, 1984-1985 (Box 532, Folder 5)
    - International Dance Council, DF-8108, 1981 (Box 533, Folder 1)
    - Oswald, Genevieve, DF-8325, 1983 (Box 533, Folder 2)
    - Dance-USA, DF-9013, 1990 (Box 533, Folder 3)
    - American Dance Festival, 1994 Dance Center Conference, EC-9304, 1993-1994 (Box 533, Folder 4)
    - Dance Theater Workshop, EC-9205, EC-9305, 1992-1993 (Box 533, Folder 5)
    - Fiorello Festival of Performing Arts, DF-9312, 1993 (Box 534, Folder 1)
    - La MaMa E. T. C., Asian Contemporary Dance Festival, DF-9399, 1993 (Box 534, Folder 2)
    - Cultural Center of the Philippines, 100-00-95032-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 534, Folder 3)
    - Faure, Laura, 517-00-97044-203.000-1, 1997 (Box 534, Folder 4)
    - Jacob's Pillow Dance Festival (For TAP), 100-00-94096-203.000-2, 473-00-94097-203.000-4, 100-00-94098-3, 100-00-94099-203.000-3, 1994 (Box 534, Folder 5)
    - National Institute of the Arts, 100-00-94025-203.000-3, Canceled 1994 December 12 (Box 534, Folder 6)
    - Sutra Dance Company, 100-00-97003-203.000-3, 1997 (Box 534, Folder 7)
    - World Dance Alliance, 100-00-95004-203.00-2, 1995 (Box 535, Folder 1)
    - Bates College-Dance Festival, 100-00-21133-203.3, 2001 (Box 535, Folder 2)
    - Cross Performance, Inc., 100-00-98119-203.1, 1998 (Box 535, Folder 3)
    - Smith, Nancy Stark, 517-00-97045-203.000-1, 1997 (Box 535, Folder 4)
    - Tipton, Jennifer, 100-00-98006-203.2, 1998 (Box 535, Folder 5)
    - World Dance Alliance, 100-00-99014-203.2, 1994 (Box 535, Folder 6)
    - Wolz, Carl, 706-00-21029-203.2, 2001 (Box 535, Folder 7)
    - AN Creative, Inc., 704-00-26090-203.1, 2006 (Box 536, Folder 1)
    - Bates College-Bates dance Festival, 100-00-23010-203.2, 2003 (Box 536, Folder 2)
    - Cross Performance, 100-00-20012, 203.2, 2000 (Box 536, Folder 3)
    - Moss, Dean, 706-00-23063-203.1, 2003 (Box 536, Folder 4)
    - New York International Ballet Competition (Box 536, Folder 5)
    - Stark-Smith, Nancy, 100-00-24002-203.3, 2004 (Box 536, Folder 6)
    - Tipton, Jennifer, 100-00-25005-203.2, 2005 (Box 536, Folder 7)
  - Cambodia, 11.2
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music, Classical Khmer Dancers of Cambodia (Box 536, Folder 8)
    - Cambodia-American Heritage Inc., DF-8447, 1984 (Box 536, Folder 9)
    - National Council for the Traditional Arts, DF-8065, 1980 (Box 635, Folder 3)
    - Jacob's Pillow Dance Festival, DF-93100, 1993 (Box 536, Folder 10)
    - US Indochina Reconciliation Project, DF-9088, 1990 (Box 537, Folder 1)
    - Cornell University, Southeast Asia Program, 100-00-94091-203.000-3, 1994 (Box 537, Folder 2)
    - Blumenthal, Eileen, EC-9008(56), 1990 (Box 537, Folder 3)
    - Shapiro, Toni, DF-9296, 1992 (Box 537, Folder 4)
    - Dance on '97, 535-00-97130-203.000-4, 1997 (Box 537, Folder 5)
    - United States-Indochina Reconciliation Project, 100-00-95023-203.000-3, 1995 (Box 537, Folder 6)